export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt:"What percentage of aircraft accidents are believed to be related to human error or human performance issues?",
        optionA:"50%-60%",
        optionB: "75%-80%" ,
        optionC :"20%-25%",
        optionD :"100%",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What does ATC stand for in aviation?",
        optionA: "Air Traffic Control",
        optionB: "Aviation Technical Committee",
        optionC: "Aircraft Takeoff Control",
        optionD: "Airborne Traffic Coordination",
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        prompt: "In regards of situational awareness errors, which level of error occurs most frequently in aviation accidents?",
        optionA: "Level 1",
        optionB: "Level 2",
        optionC: "Level 3",
        optionD: "All levels occur equally",
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the purpose of the VFR (Visual Flight Rules) in aviation?",
        optionA: "To regulate air traffic at night",
        optionB: "To control flights over mountainous areas",
        optionC: "To establish communication protocols",
        optionD: "To govern aircraft operations in visual conditions",
        answer: "D"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the primary cause of errors related to situational awareness?",
        optionA: "Pilot inattention",
        optionB: "Lack of communication",
        optionC: "Relevant data not being available to the pilot",
        optionD: "Technical failures",
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        prompt: "In aviation, what does ILS stand for?",
        optionA: "Instrument Landing System",
        optionB: "International Landing Standards",
        optionC: "Integrated Logistics Support",
        optionD: "Inflight Landing Sequence",
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        prompt: "In a study on pilot training, what was identified as the main influence contributing to pilot fatigue?",
        optionA: "Age",
        optionB: "Lack of proper training",
        optionC: "Long working days and insufficient sleep",
        optionD: "Gender",
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the primary function of the altimeter in an aircraft?",
        optionA: "Measure airspeed",
        optionB: "Indicate altitude",
        optionC: "Control engine power",
        optionD: "Monitor fuel consumption",
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        prompt: "How does a comprehensive pre-flight inspection contribute to aviation safety?",
        optionA: "Enhances fuel efficiency",
        optionB: "Spot and fix problems",
        optionC: "Improves in-flight entertainment",
        optionD: "Conducting taste tests of in-flight meals",
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is a crucial aspect of continuous training for pilots of single-prop airplanes?",
        optionA: "Monitoring weather conditions",
        optionB: "Learning aerobatic maneuvers",
        optionC: "Keeping up with fashion trends",
        optionD: "Staying updated on tech and safety",
        answer: "D"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Why is terrain awareness and avoidance emphasized for the safe operation of single-prop airplanes?",
        optionA: "Improves Pilot's Eyesights",
        optionB: "Reduce collisions with obstacles",
        optionC: "Increase aircraft speed",
        optionD: "Entertain passengers with terrain views",
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Why is adhering to correct communication protocols crucial for pilots of single-prop aircraft?",
        optionA: "Impress air traffic controllers",
        optionB: "Make conversations interesting",
        optionC: "Guarantee precise communication",
        optionD: "Test radio equipment",
        answer: "C"
    },
]

